Stop it. Stop celebrating me!
(Voice:)Woo!
And no woos!
Not you, Dr. Woo, you're fins.
(Sheldon:)I want you all to know that
you have no reason to applaud me.
(Sheldon:)My so-called breakthrough
wasn't the result of my genius.
(Sheldon:)It was nothing more
than a boneheaded mistake.
(Sheldon:)So please refrain from praising me
for it in the future.
(Raj:)I don't understand.
They didn't End the element?
(Sheldon:)No, they found the element.
No, no, stop it!
(Sheldon:)I don't need to take this admiration
from the likes of you people!
(Sheldon:)-How do I make them stop loving me?
-Invite them to live with us.
(Penny:)Boy, Bernadette is gonna love this.
(Leonard:)It must be nice to have someone
do something so romantic.
(Penny:)Okay, you know what's not romantic?
(Penny:)Rubbing it in someone's face.
(Leonard:)Actually, it can be,
but I told you sex doesn't count.